<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<set gameId="845bfe7f-477e-4c53-9526-6ffe2ceeb5d9" gameVersion="1.1.0.0" id="f83804e0-0d73-4cc5-8377-e2df3e331d49" name="Box Powers" version="1.0"><cards><card id="fac18b34-6f1b-4a9f-bba8-c8393db48f9d" name="Huntress"><property name="Allegiance" value="Smoke Jaguar"/><property name="Text">{T}: Scrap a card from your hand to choose one of your 'Mechs. That 'Mech may attack as if it were one speed faster this turn. Use this ability during your Missions phase, but not during a mission.</property></card><card id="a04fd2c8-23db-4663-9e42-4e716c7955fc" name="Strana Mechty"><property name="Allegiance" value="Wolf"/><property name="Text">{T}: crap a card from your hand to choose one of your 'Mechs. Re-roll all of the missile dice for that 'Mech. Use this ability only after all of the missile dice for that 'Mech have been rolled.</property></card><card id="7ae36e73-f37e-418b-a97b-a537e1d9972c" name="Ironhold"><property name="Allegiance" value="Jade Falcon"/><property name="Text">{T}: Scrap a card from your hand to repair up to 3 damage to each of your Units. Use this ability only during your Repair/Reload phase.</property></card><card id="c7a13358-803a-4ff6-a309-b82f30c86820" name="Ghost Bear"><property name="Allegiance" value="Alshain"/><property name="Text">{T}: Scrap a card from your hand to activate a 'Mech in your Construction Region that is fully constructed. Put a +1 attack counter on it for every 3 construction counters above its cost. Use this ability only during your Deploy phase.</property></card><card id="36836ffc-4f08-4860-b961-bf79876236cf" name="Terra"><property name="Allegiance" value="ComStar"/><property name="Text">{T}: Scrap a card from your hand to look at your opponent's hand and discard one card at random from his or her hand. Use this ability during your Missions phase, but not during a mission.</property></card><card id="51314dbe-0b38-4fb5-9954-0059b3e22624" name="New Avalon"><property name="Allegiance" value="Davion"/><property name="Text">{T}: Scrap a card from your hand to get +2 initiative. Use this ability only during a mission.</property></card><card id="a33477bd-683a-43d7-a3b2-ff4686cda5a2" name="Tharkad"><property name="Allegiance" value="Steiner"/><property name="Text">{T}: Scrap a card from your hand to gain {R}. Use this ability only during your Deploy phase.</property></card><card id="8dec2a37-83da-4075-b2f3-fbec4cf1fda4" name="Kurita"><property name="Allegiance" value="Luthien"/><property name="Text">{T}: Scrap a card from your hand to give your attacking 'Mech +1 attack. Use this ability only during a Mission, and only if that 'Mech is attacking alone.</property></card><card id="1e339f84-4327-493c-9258-5f3e7db57b2c" name="Liao"><property name="Allegiance" value="Liao"/><property name="Text">{T}: Scrap a card from your hand to give your opponent -1 initiative. Use this ability only during a mission.</property></card><card id="9ccbaa6c-d1a2-462c-8d74-c4df2a8ee172" name="St. Ives"><property name="Allegiance" value="St. Ives"/><property name="Text">{T}: Scrap a card from your hand to gain A, L, M, P, and T until end of turn. Use this ability only during your Deploy phase.</property></card><card id="b584c655-a0b5-4733-9569-5c0e1c678d93" name="Rasalhague"><property name="Allegiance" value="Rasalhague"/><property name="Text">{T}: Scrap a card from your hand to have a Command card that deals damage deal +1 total damage. Use this ability only when you activate that card.</property></card><card id="492b5c91-5162-4dfd-b05a-d62d055d433f" name="Marik"><property name="Allegiance" value="Marik"/><property name="Text">{T}: Scrap a card from your hand to give one of your Units Long-Range 2. (If that Unit is blocked, it may deal 2 of its damage to the target.) Use this ability only during a mission.</property></card><card id="7ef243e9-2b99-4d4f-9a9f-97af2af0aa94" name="Steel Viper"><property name="Allegiance" value="Steel Viper"/><property name="Text">{T}: Scrap a card from your hand to search your Stockpile for any Unit card. Show that card to all players, put it into your hand, and shuffle your Stockpile. Then choose any Unit card in your hand, show it to all players, and restock it. Use this ability only during your Deploy phase.</property></card></cards></set>